vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com 2019-04-05

# vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com website's Privacy Policy

Vegetarian cooking recipes found at https://www.vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

At "vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com"  we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use "vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com", as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

"vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com" strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.   

## Collection of Personal Information Privacy policy

**"vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com" collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis.** Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name and email address . 

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. 

[Go to top of this ](https://www.vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com/privacy-policy.html)privacy policy page 

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be **used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties**. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website. 

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads. This cookie enables Google to serve ads to users based on their visits to sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).   

## Use of Cookies  

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. 

A cookie is a string of information that vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.

[Go to top of this ](https://www.vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com/privacy-policy.html)privacy policy page

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Taking this action shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

### **Google Analytics Cookies**

We may serve third party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our website to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose. 

The search box on this web site ("Search Box") is powered by Google Inc. ("Google"). You acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy (located at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.

vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com also uses Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all of your comments and may show them on your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings. You can view [Facebook Privacy Policies](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). 

You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.  

If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.  

We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

 This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

[Go to top](https://www.vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com/privacy-policy.html) of this privacy policy page 

## Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our userbase as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.  

## Release of Information

If "vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com" is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation inour site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.  

## How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on these links  

## Updates and Effective Date

"vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com" reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.  

## Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to "vegetarian-cooking-recipes-tips.com" Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

* * *

* * *
